<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Piyush Sharma</title>
    <link>http://localhost:38967/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Piyush Sharma</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 02:15:27 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:38967/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Community Bonding and Week 01 Progress</title>
      <link>http://localhost:38967/post/community-bonding-and-week-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 02:15:27 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:38967/post/community-bonding-and-week-01/</guid>
      <description>This post documents the planning of the project, my learnings during the community bonding period, and the tasks I completed in my first week.&#xA;Community Bonding Period After the euphoria of being accepted into GSoC faded, it was time for setting up my workspace and diving back into the codebase after a month. Planning out the project was key, and meeting with my mentors was a big part of that. I was excited for this chat because the mentors had been super helpful and easy to reach during the proposal stage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting Selected for Google Summer of Code 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:38967/post/getting-selected-for-gsoc_2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 16:11:56 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:38967/post/getting-selected-for-gsoc_2024/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone, this marks my first blog post where I pen down my experience and learnings about getting selected for Google Summer of Code.&#xA;What is this series about? In this series of blog posts, I mainly plan on walking you through what it was like working for GSoC, what challenges I faced, and how I overcame those.&#xA;Google Summer of Code is a global, online program focused on bringing new contributors into open source software development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venturing Forward : Test Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:38967/post/venturing-forward/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:17:06 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:38967/post/venturing-forward/</guid>
      <description>Stay posted for future updates :).</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
